<?xml version="1.0"?>
<catalogue>
    <message key="blogname_rssfeed">Name of the blog for the RSS feed. If empty, 'sitename' is taken.</message>
    <message key="desc_rssfeed">Description  for the RSS feed. If empty, 'sitedescription' is taken.</message>
    <message key="motiv_help"><![CDATA[More themes available at <a href="http://intensivstation.ch/en/templates/bxcms/" target="_blank">intensivstation.ch</a>.
                              <br/>(Hover over the picture to see a larger version).]]></message>
    <message key="default_blogcommentmode">Default Blog post comment mode. You can change this for each post individually later.</message>
    
    <!--<message key="blogCaptchaFontPath">The path to your font dir</message>
    <message key="blogCaptchaFontFile">The name of you font file</message>-->
    <message key="help_blogSendRejectedCommentNotification">Send a notification mail on rejected comments. The Flux CMS comment spam protection tries
           hard to determine, if a comment is spam or not. If it rejects one, it's almost certainly spam and you most certainly
           don't want to be informed about that. If it's not sure, Flux CMS sets the post to moderated and you always get a mail then and you can then approve it.</message>
    
    <message key="help_blogCaptchaAfterDays">After how many days captcha should be activated. (-1 = never)</message>
    <message key="help_blogAkismetKey"><![CDATA[As an additional comment-spam check, you can use the <a href="http://akismet.com">akismet</a> service. You have to get an API key at <a href="http://wordpress.com/signup/">http://wordpress.com/signup/</a> and insert that here.]]></message> 
    <message key="help_openIdEnabled">Should OpenID verification be enabled for blog comments.</message>
    <message key="help_copyright">Who holds the copyright of your content?</message>
    <message key="help_cclink"><![CDATA[If you want to use a <a href='http://creativecommons.org/'>Creative Commons</a> license for your blog content, put the link to the license here. Eg. http://creativecommons.org/licenses/by/2.5/]]> </message>
    <message key="help_timezoneseconds"> Your timezone in seconds (eg. 3600). 'servertime' means server timezone.</message>
    <message key="help_timezonestring">Your timezone as string (eg. CET). 'servertime' means server timezone.</message>
    <message key="help_icbm"><![CDATA[Your geolocation. It's basically "Latitude, Longitude" (47.3798, 8.5275 for the Bitflux office). If you don't know your coordinates, go to 
    <a target='_new' href='http://multimap.com'>Multimap.com</a>, search your place and copy the data from the box on the bottom called "Map Information".]]></message>
    <message key="help_outputlanguages">Available output languages (semicolon separated 2 letter codes)</message>
    <message key="help_defaultlanguage">Default language (a 2 letter code from above)</message>
    <message key="help_detectbrowserlanguage">Automatic browser language detection</message>
    <message key="help_image_allowed_sizes">Allowed image sizes for dynamic resizing</message>
    <message key="Blog Default Editor">We highly recommend the WYSIWYG (what you see is what you get) editor, if you're not familiar with HTML. It also has more features than the Source Editor. The WYSIWYG Editor automatically falls back to the Source Editor, if your browser doesn't support it.</message>
<message key="help_blogWeblogsPing">Which services to ping.</message>
<message key="help_blogShowOnlyOneLanguage">Should only blogposts in the selected language be shown? No = All posts in all languages are always shown. Not relevant if you only blog in one language.</message> 
</catalogue>
